Boys of Abu Ghraib is a drama, war, thriller film directed by Luke Moran.
An American soldier deployed at Abu Ghraib finds himself behind the walls of the infamous
Hard Site, where he develops a secret friendship with an Iraqi detainee.
Jack Farmer, played by Luke Moran.
Tanner, played by Sean Astin.
Peyton, played by Sara Paxton.
Pits, played by Michael Welch.
Sam Farmer, played by John Heard.
Tunde, played by Elijah Kelley.
Boys of Abu Ghraib is a 2014 American war film inspired by the events that took place at the
Abu Ghraib prison in Baghdad, Iraq in 2003, in the background of the Iraq war.
It was written and directed by Luke Moran, who co-stars alongside
Sean Astin, Omid Abtahi, Sara Paxton, and John Heard.
Filmmakers Edward Zwick and Marshall Herskovitz served as executive producers
on the film, which was produced by Luke Moran and Cru Ennis.
The tone is emotional and intense.